jobsvilli.com 2012-05-03

# Jobs in Pakistan | Find Jobs in Pakistan Karachi Lahore Islamabad

## Privacy Policy

The privacy policy outlined here is applicable to all visitors to this website (jobsvilli.com). The terms 'we' and 'our' refer to jobsvilli, while the terms 'you' and 'your' refer to the visitors of this site. This policy governs the purpose(s) of collecting information, the method(s) of information collection, and the use of this information. Using or accessing jobsvilli.com implies that you have read and understood our privacy policy and you agree with its contents. In case you do not agree, please avoid using this website.

We reserve the right to revise the policy as and when necessary. Users are advised to periodically review this section. A modification notice stays on this website's landing page for at least 30 days.

Use of Collected and Stored Information

We collect personal and non-personal information from users of this site to give them quality services. Other reasons for collecting your personal and non-personal information include analysis of your demographics, maintain constant communication with the users, etc.

Personal Information

Personal information includes name, location, contact numbers, academic backgrounds, career achievements, etc. that you put in a subscription form. We also gather the data directly from resumes you agree to upload on this site. We use this information to send you job alters based on your interest and preferences. You can unsubscribe to the service anytime. The information is gathered in database and used to deliver you the best product and services and prepare research reports. The services may include promotional offers. We do not sell or rent personal information to any third party.

Nonpersonal Information

This includes the addresses (URL) of the websites visited before and after visiting our website, your IP address, your browser information, etc. 

Cookie

To improve your interaction with our website and to make it more personalized, we use 'cookies'-a small text file created by an internet site to store relevant information in your computer's hard drive.

A cookie helps us identify you every time you visit the website. This login or registration information eases your frequent visit to our site. Cookies are not used to deliver viruses or run programs in your computer. These are exclusively assigned and read by web server only. Most internet browsers allow you to delete the cookies, block cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.

Information Sharing

The nonpersonal information may be shared with the third party advertising service providers, our partners, etc.

Third-party advertisers may also store cookies on your computer while serving advertisements and marketing messages. The cookies stored by them are beyond our control and not governed by the terms of this privacy policy.

Rest assured we do not give third party advertisers access to your personal information. 

Security

Personal information is safely kept on secure servers which are accessible to only selected authorized personnel. We use secure socket layer (SSL) to encrypt sensitive information.

While we make every possible effort to ensure the security of your data, we do not guarantee its security nor do we take responsibility for any loss or misuse of the information during transmission to and from our website.

Contact Us:

For further information, please feel free to write us at support@jobsvilli.com
